[{"answer": "You can dare to dream all you want, but I don't want you to have those hopes crushed as soon as you get them up, Piers, because we've all seen movies like this before in Washington.", "docId": "131008pmt", "aSentId": 22, "question": "Can I dare to dream?", "qSentId": 21}, {"answer": "You know, because they're not speaking to one another, it's a very hard question to answer.", "docId": "131008pmt", "aSentId": 36, "question": "Does the government reopen pending those deliberations?", "qSentId": 35}, {"answer": "Well, there's absolutely nothing the matter.", "docId": "131008pmt", "aSentId": 55, "question": "What is the matter with them?", "qSentId": 54}, {"answer": "ORGAN: OK, we'll do a deal.", "docId": "131008pmt", "aSentId": 142, "question": "They are lying items in a budget and if you are going to look at a budget, at appropriations, at a funding mechanism you have to say, \"Where are we spending this money?", "qSentId": 141}, {"answer": "I'll throw it out.", "docId": "131008pmt", "aSentId": 149, "question": "Where is the point where you think this could be honorably settled?", "qSentId": 148}, {"answer": "I'm calling an end to this.", "docId": "131008pmt", "aSentId": 189, "question": "... where can we get these reductions?", "qSentId": 188}, {"answer": "I'm a lot better than I was, I'll tell you that.", "docId": "131008pmt", "aSentId": 212, "question": "Now, Cathy I know that you're speaking from your hospital bed, how are you physically?", "qSentId": 211}, {"answer": "Well, I think that what really, really got to me and, you know, first we see people every year, the same people every year who were having the shutdown very reluctantly of something that they truly believe in.", "docId": "131008pmt", "aSentId": 246, "question": "How do you feel about the Washington politicians which are causing all this disruption all over your country leading in your case to a potentially very serious situation?", "qSentId": 245}, {"answer": "Or it's the calm that comes from believing that there is no storm coming.", "docId": "131008pmt", "aSentId": 271, "question": "But is it -- but it's the calm before the storm, isn't it?", "qSentId": 270}, {"answer": "That's a ridiculous analogy, but I was very glad that ...", "docId": "131008pmt", "aSentId": 291, "question": "And Kelly on a certain sympathy when I heard President Obama said today, you know, it's like somebody fire bombing your house, stealing all your possessions, taking your car, and they're saying let's negotiate, what's the matter with you?", "qSentId": 290}, {"answer": "I'm speaking to a couple of groups in our senate right meeting in Iowa's is tomorrow morning.", "docId": "131008pmt", "aSentId": 306, "question": "Is this part of a secret plan to run for the White House?", "qSentId": 305}, {"answer": "Yeah, look we take a deep breath, every president has negotiated on debt ceilings.", "docId": "131008pmt", "aSentId": 310, "question": "So, look, I'm up for a short-term debt deal, what is that deal likely to be, likely to be?", "qSentId": 309}, {"answer": "Well, number one, we've had the house since 1979 but we never ever stayed down there except maybe 26 days out of the first 13 years because we had a ranch and we were busy and we didn't really get to go down there that much.", "docId": "131008pmt", "aSentId": 341, "question": "He's been having treatment for cancer and no cartilage left in his knees, what do you make of this Joyce?", "qSentId": 340}, {"answer": "I'm very frustrated.", "docId": "131008pmt", "aSentId": 350, "question": "What do you feel about what's happened to your parents?", "qSentId": 349}, {"answer": "He's lost his trust in everything at this point.", "docId": "131008pmt", "aSentId": 362, "question": "Why is that?", "qSentId": 361}, {"answer": "My parents are relocated into town.", "docId": "131008pmt", "aSentId": 368, "question": "And where are they living in the moment, your parents?", "qSentId": 367}, {"answer": "It's not even work.", "docId": "131008pmt", "aSentId": 463, "question": "Marc Lamont Hill, what are worst things about this?", "qSentId": 462}, {"answer": "Well, then if businesses don't get subsidies.", "docId": "131008pmt", "aSentId": 512, "question": "Oh, so you're doing it because you haven't been able to get the subsidies ready for the businesses?", "qSentId": 511}, {"answer": "They always get paid.", "docId": "131008pmt", "aSentId": 536, "question": "They came out today and said, \"Wow, this is really worrying, America may not pay as back the money,\" (inaudible) right?", "qSentId": 535}, {"answer": "Oh yeah, and it's embarrassing, but I think we're not at a point yet where it's really impacting the willingness of people to buy our bonds, I think we've been able to explain to the Chinese and the Japanese that they will get paid in a way that has them laughing at us a little bit, but it doesn't have them panicking yet.", "docId": "131008pmt", "aSentId": 540, "question": "So last people who get paid will be the Americans on Social Security, I mean this is a fuzz, isn't it?", "qSentId": 539}]